<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title></title>
		<description>Damon Bauer - Front End Developer from Nashville, TN. Writing primarily about CSS, Scss and JavaScript. Pretend woodworker. Mountain bike poseur.</description>
		<link>http://damonbauer.me</link>
		<atom:link href="http://damonbauer.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Migrating code from ES3 &amp;rarr; ES5 &amp;rarr; ES6</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been trying to find ways to make small gains in my overall understanding of JavaScript. While working on a code sample for a different blog post, I knew there was probably a way to improve what I’d written, so I reached out to &lt;a href=&quot;1&quot;&gt;a friend&lt;/a&gt; to get some advice.
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://damonbauer.me/migrating-from-es3-es5-es6/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://damonbauer.me/migrating-from-es3-es5-es6/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>CSS Scroll Snapping</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;From Sergey Gospodarets:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; Scroll snapping is used widely for a better separation of the provided content (vertical full height pages) or, for example, to emulate galleries behavior.&lt;br&gt; &amp;hellip;&lt;br&gt; Can you imagine how easy would be creating such effects using CSS only? Meet the &lt;a href=&quot;http://dev.w3.org/csswg/css-snappoints/&quot;&gt;CSS Scroll Snap Points specification&lt;/a&gt;! &lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://damonbauer.me/css-scroll-snap/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://damonbauer.me/css-scroll-snap/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>GitHub Patchwork: Nashville</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;This week, I had the opportunity to attend a GitHub Patchwork event in Nashville, TN, where I call home. At first, I was apprehensive about going; I’m typically shy and feel as if I don’t have much to offer at an event with people I’m not familiar with. However, after talking with a few friends about the event, I decided that it would be a good thing to experience. Myself and my coworker &amp;amp; friend &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/buddylreno&quot;&gt;Buddy&lt;/a&gt; both signed up to serve as mentors as we both have a good bit of history working with Git &amp;amp; GitHub.
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://damonbauer.me/github-patchwork/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://damonbauer.me/github-patchwork/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Chrome Filmstrip &amp; Improving Page Speed</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;You may have heard of the wonderful site, &lt;a href=&quot;http://webpagetest.org&quot;&gt;WebpageTest&lt;/a&gt;, when researching ways to improve your site performance. One of the most useful features (in my opinion) is the Filmstrip; it shows you incremental screenshots of the browser rendering your site, so you can see how quickly users are able to start consuming content. As of the past couple of months, you can enable similar functionality in Chrome!
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://damonbauer.me/chrome-filmstrip/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://damonbauer.me/chrome-filmstrip/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>What is BrowserSync and How Do You Use it?</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;If you’ve not used &lt;a href=&quot;http://browsersync.io&quot;&gt;BrowserSync&lt;/a&gt; in your daily workflow, you’re missing out. It’s become an indispensible tool for me in the past two years by improving efficiency and reducing cross browser inconsistencies. In this post, I’ll introduce BrowserSync and explore a few use cases that I use on a regular basis.
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://damonbauer.me/browsersync/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://damonbauer.me/browsersync/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Is There a &amp;ldquo;Better&amp;rdquo; Text Decoration?</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking to change the thickness, color, opacity or position of &lt;code&gt;text-decoration&lt;/code&gt;? While the following technique isn’t &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; using this property, I’m going to demonstrate a way to fake some neat visual changes that simulate this property and take it a step further.
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://damonbauer.me/better-text-decoration/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://damonbauer.me/better-text-decoration/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Organizing Jekyll Pages</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;I realize I’m pretty late to the game, but &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; is great. I’ve tried various blogging platforms &amp;amp; tools in the past, but since making the switch to Jekyll a few months ago, I’ve been encouraged to keep writing. One thing that has bugged me about using Jekyll is the way it’s set up to handle static pages. No more!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://damonbauer.me/organizing-jekyll-pages/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://damonbauer.me/organizing-jekyll-pages/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Implementing an SVG Icon System</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;In the last few months, &lt;abbr title=&quot;Scalable Vector Graphics&quot;&gt;SVG&lt;/abbr&gt; has started to once again gain traction in the world of front end development&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#footnote-1&quot; name=&quot;fn-1&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, thanks in part to the amazing work of some &lt;a href=&quot;https://css-tricks.com/mega-list-svg-information/&quot;&gt;very&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://sarasoueidan.com/articles/index.html&quot;&gt;smart&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://tutorials.jenkov.com/svg/svg-and-css.html&quot;&gt;people&lt;/a&gt;. For some time now, I’ve wanted a way to replace icon fonts with more a semantic, accessible and performant solution while maintaining the resolution independence and ease of use that comes with using them. I’ve been exploring the world of SVG and trying to find a solution that is easy to implement &amp;amp; maintain, light, and cross-browser compatible.
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://damonbauer.me/implementing-svg/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://damonbauer.me/implementing-svg/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Click to Reveal Search Bar</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;In the interest in of feature parity between desktop &amp;amp; mobile experiences, I’ve recently been working on adding search to the mobile view of my employer’s website, &lt;a href=&quot;http://daveramsey.com&quot;&gt;daveramsey.com&lt;/a&gt;. The following is an explanation of why and how I am going about adding an click-to-reveal search bar on small screens.
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://damonbauer.me/click-to-reveal-search-bar/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://damonbauer.me/click-to-reveal-search-bar/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Git Interactive Add</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;There are numerous extra scripts that come with Git that can help you create more meaningful, specific commits to your repositories. One such script is “interactive” add, which I recently discovered while working on a project.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://damonbauer.me/git-interactive-add/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://damonbauer.me/git-interactive-add/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
